

KARPOVICH IRINA

JUNIOR QA ENGINEER

PERSONAL PROFILE

I am constantly engaged in self-education, have experience of speaking at conferences, I am the author of 12 scientific publications, a participant in advanced training courses, and also the winner of 2 places in the competition of professional skills (2010).

CONTACT

- Minsk, Belarus
- irina-klimovskih@yandex.ru
- +375 (29) 331-56-90
- in /in/irina-karpovich/
- github.com/IrinaKarpovich

LANGUAGES

Russian - Native English - A2

SKILLS

- SDLC. STLC
- Software development methodologies and processes
- Basic Test Design Techniques (EP, BVA, CE, EG)
- Basic documentation (Checklist, Test Cases, Test Suite, Bug report, TRR)
- MS Office (Word, Excel and etc.)
- Functional Testing of Web Applications
- Client-Server Architecture
- JSON, XML, HTML, DevTools
- TMS (Test Link)
- Basic SQL queries
- Postman, Fiddler, GIT

COURSES

"Software Testing" course, "STORMNET" IT Academy FEB 2021 - MAR 2021

WORK EXPERIENCE

Institution of preschool education No. 56 of Grodno,Speech therapist

Diagnosis of speech disorders, preparation of correctional programs, work on correcting speech defects in children SEP 2019 - JUN 2020

Yanka Kupala State University of Grodno, Faculty of Pedagogy, Lecturer

Study of state programs education, development of test tasks for students, preparation of reporting documentation

NOV 2011 - MAY 2019

EDUCATION

Yanka Kupala State University of Grodno, second degree of higher education, "General pedagogy, history of pedagogy and education"
SEP 2011 - JUN 2013

Belarusian State Pedagogical University Named after Maxim Tank (BSPU), Institute of inclusive education, speech therapist, psychologist SEP 2005 - JUN 2010